

# **BREE BROWDER**

UI/UX DESIGNER ♥ TULSA, OK ६ (918) 417-2259

#### • CONTACT •

Tulsa, OK (918) 417-2259 <u>browder.bree@gmail.com</u>

o LINKS o

**Portfolio** 

**Github** 

LinkedIn

#### • SKILLS •

User research and user strategy

Information architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Figma

Adobe XD

User testing

UI design

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Responsive web design

### PROFILE

Empathy-driven problem solver with a focus on strong, agile collaboration with business users and technical teams to realize a vision that can foster meaningful experiences for stakeholders and enable success. Background in both high and low level coding languages.

## EDUCATION

### Google UX Design Professional Certificate, Coursera

January 2022 — June 2022

- Achieved the <u>RISE</u> scholarship, an award program committed to accelerating equity for moms and women of color by providing access to upskill tech certifications.
- Gained deep experience through over 200 hours of instruction and hundreds of real world UX design scenarios that included practice-based activities and assessments.

**Diploma of Computer Science & Full Stack Web Development, Holberton School, Tulsa** September 2020 — June 2022

- Completed a rigorous, fast-paced <u>software development curriculum</u> focused on project-based, peer learning.
- Programmed in a hybrid learning environment, both online and on campus in an extended 20-month long coding bootcamp.
- Collaborated to complete deliverables and meet deadlines that simulated a real working environment.
- Languages studied: Bash, C, Python, JS, HTML, CSS.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Web Design Intern at Reed Design Group, Mansfield

March 2022 — Present

- Explored competitor websites to determine how they compared to assigned web analysis tasks and recommended detailed improvements to both form and substance.
- Prototyped and wireframed new design ideas for websites.

# **★** PROJECTS

## Mobile Gym App: Case Study

February 2022 — March 2022

Designed a specialized gym application from scratch, beginning with user research and ending with high fidelity prototypes in Figma. The Rocket Labs™ Fitness Application helps users from a larger demographic seek a more active lifestyle by accommodating for needs that have not yet been met by the market.

· Links: Presentation, Figma Designs

#### **Holberton Smiling School**

October 2021

Implemented a designers Figma prototype from scratch in order to create a fully functional product that mirrors the design as closely as possible. The dynamic web application was created with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, and a preconfigured API.

• Link: Holberton-Smiling-School v2